MATTHEW ENDALL

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Canberra ACT Australia

PHONE

0404709119

EMAIL

matt.j.endall@gmail.com

LINKS

Pangea Movement

SKILLS

Excellent Work Ethic

Teamwork Skills

Strong Mathematical Skills

Programming (Python, HTML/CSS & JS, C)

HOBBIES

Language Learning
Web Development
Ardunio & Raspberry Pi
Prototyping
Exercise/Sport
(Skateboarding,
Weightlifting, etc.)

LANGUAGES

English

Japanese

Indonesian

PROFILE

Dedicated and high achieving current student at the Australian National University. Abundance of experience working various roles within a team environment. Adept in many programming and office technologies, with an eagerness to expand my knowledge. Exceptional communication skills and the ability to converse in three languages.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Development, Pangea Movement

Bali, Indonesia.

Apr 2022 — Feb 2023

I was contracted to work as the web developer for a start-up outdoor apparel and gear company in Bali, Indonesia. The web development team was a group of 3, where I was provided with Figma designs that I used to implement a responsive and interactive design to Pangea's shopify e-commerce website. Software used included Pagefly, HTML, JS and CSS. See website from link section.

Private Mathematics Tutor

Canberra, ACT.

Jan 2020 — Dec 2021

I have experience tutoring students ranging from years 7-12. I developed personal lesson plans for each student, and reviewed their marked assessment items to determine strengths and weaknesses to improve further lessons. I frequently received positive feedback on the improvement of students' performance.

Delivery Driver, Dominos Australia

Florey, ACT.

Aug 2018 — Jun 2019

My main role was as a delivery driver. The position also involved tasks such as washing dishes and assisting managers in opening and closing the store. Throughout my employment I also took it upon myself to acquire various skills to assist all team members (pizza making and preparation, dough making, and order taking).

EDUCATION

Flexible Double Degree (Engineering), Australian National University

Canberra, ACT.

Current 4th year student with a 6.31 GPA and 81.3 WAM. Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) intending on majoring in mechatronics, and Bachelor of Languages majoring in Japanese.

REFERENCES

References available upon request